Mitch Raznick

FULL-STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PROJECTS

Virtual Art Institute of Chicago — Deployed | FE Github | BE Github

Full-stack group project with content sourced from the Art Institute of Chicago's public API. My primary role was building front-end logic using React.

Directory of Astronauts — <u>Deployed</u> (JSON Viewer Suggested)| <u>Github</u>

Built a simplified version of NASA's API using Mongoose, Express, and Axios. Includes CRUD functionality and RESTful routes.

Duck Hunt — Deployed | Github

Front-end project for rebuilding a functional web-based version of the classic Duck Hunt video game. Languages used were HTML, JavaScript, and CSS.

EXPERIENCE

General Assembly, New York, NY - Software Engineering Fellow

MAY 2022 - AUG 2022

Completed over 480 of coding, and built around 35 web apps, programs, and sites over the course of 13 weeks as part of the Software Engineering Immersive program

ButterflyMX, New York, NY - Sales Director

JAN 2022 - MAY 2022

Prospected 50+ multi-family real estate leads per day; Managed a pipeline via Salesforce and HubSpot sequences; Built and presented a sales deck and software demo of our smart intercoms 3-6 times per day to developers, owners, property managers, and more; Generated over \$10K ARR in my first quarter.

Angi Leads, New York, NY — *Inside Sales Manager*

JULY 2018 - DEC 2021

Developed and managed a team of 10-14 reps for B2B sales; Used datamining software to generate and distribute thousands of leads per week; Selected to lead org- and office-wide workshops for various best practices; Awarded Alpha Cup (top sales team) in December 2018; Tracked and analyzed weekly sales data to successfully improve metrics and performance, and achieved highest-revenue manager in Q3 2021 following a re-brand from HomeAdvisor and verticalization.

Angi Leads, New York, NY — Senior Online Marketing Consultant

JUNE 2016 - JULY 2018

Made over 250 lifetime B2B sales by using best practices in CRM pipeline management, pitching strategies, and outreach methods; Served as team lead and secondary coach alongside team manager; Built member profiles using SEO terms to boost consumer interaction; Four-time MVP winner in director group;

CONTACT & PORTFOLIO

mraznick@gmail.com Portfolio Github 402-980-4919 Brooklyn, NY

LANGUAGES & FRAMEWORKS

HTML CSS

JavaScript React

Python Node.js

Mongoose MongoDB

Express Axios

Django Flask

SQL Postgres

Netlify Heroku

SUMMARY

I'm a creative, problem-solving, impact-driven developer with an eye for design. I'm able to leverage my 6 years in tech sales to exhibit great skills in communication, delivery, and teamwork. My career change from tech sales to software engineering is fueled by my creative foundation and educational background, my passion to build, and the analytical mindset gained from tech sales. I can bring efficiency and poise to fast-paced environments to achieve team goals with tight deadlines.

EDUCATION

General Assembly NYC Software Engineering Immersive MAY 2022 - AUG 2022

The University of Kansas William Allen White School of Journalism BS in Journalism: News & Information Minor in Film & Media Studies AUG 2011 - AUG 2015